<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="menu_measurement_guidance">How to measure</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_screen_title">How to measure</string>
    <string name="cd_metric_info">Show measurement guidance</string>

    <string name="measurement_guidance_weight">Weigh yourself at <b>the same time of day (ideally in the morning after getting up and after using the toilet)</b> and without clothing or with very light clothing. Stand centered on the scale and remain still until the reading is stable.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_body_fat">Use a body fat scale and make sure you <b>stand barefoot with clean, dry feet on the electrodes</b>. Measure under the same conditions whenever possible (time of day, hydration), as the reading is strongly influenced by these factors.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_neck_circumference">Look straight ahead and relax your shoulders. Measure the neck circumference <b>directly below the larynx (Adam\'s apple)</b>. Keep the measuring tape horizontal.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: <b>directly below the Adam\'s apple</b>\n♀ Women: <b>at the narrowest point of the neck</b> (if the Adam\'s apple is not clearly visible)</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_chest_circumference">Stand upright and breathe normally - measure at the end of a normal exhale. The measuring tape should be horizontal.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: circumference <b>at nipple level</b>\n♀ Women: circumference <b>at the fullest part of the chest</b>; ideally wear an <b>unpadded bra or no bra</b></string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_waist_circumference">Find the lowest palpable rib of your rib cage and the highest point of your hip bone. Stand relaxed and breathe out normally. Measure the circumference <b>midway between the rib cage and hip</b>. Keep the measuring tape horizontal and do not pull it too tight.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_abdomen_circumference">Stand upright and relax your abdomen. Measure the circumference <b>directly at navel level</b>. The measuring tape should be horizontal.\n\n⚠️ Note: This measurement differs from the waist circumference - it is always taken at the navel.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_hip_circumference">Stand upright with feet together. Measure the circumference <b>at the widest point of the hips and buttocks</b>. Make sure the measuring tape remains horizontal.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_chest_skinfold">Grasp the skin <b>midway between the nipple and the fold that forms between the arm and chest</b> when the arm hangs down. Grasp so that the measured skin fold runs from the nipple toward the armpit.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>diagonally</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: <b>measure as described</b>\n♀ Women: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_abdomen_skinfold">Grasp the skin <b>approx. 2-3 cm to the right of the navel</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>vertically</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: <b>measure as described</b>\n♀ Women: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_thigh_skinfold">Stand relaxed and shift your weight to the other leg. Grasp the skin <b>on the front of the thigh, approximately midway between the hip and the knee</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>vertically</b>.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_triceps_skinfold">Let the arm hang loosely. Grasp the skin <b>on the back of the upper arm, midway between the shoulder and elbow</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>vertically</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♀ Women: <b>measure as described</b>\n♂ Men: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_suprailiac_skinfold">Grasp the skin <b>directly above the hip bone, running slightly diagonally downward toward the front</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>diagonally</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♀ Women: <b>measure as described</b>\n♂ Men: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
</resources>
