<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="menu_measurement_guidance">How to measure</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_screen_title">How to measure</string>
    <string name="menu_health_rating_guide">Analysis result guide</string>
    <string name="health_rating_guide_title">Analysis Result Guide</string>

    <!-- Health Rating Guide Section Titles -->
    <string name="health_rating_section_body_fat_male">Body Fat % (Male)</string>
    <string name="health_rating_section_body_fat_female">Body Fat % (Female)</string>
    <string name="health_rating_section_whr_male">Waist-Hip Ratio (Male)</string>
    <string name="health_rating_section_whr_female">Waist-Hip Ratio (Female)</string>

    <!-- Rating Descriptions — BMI -->
    <string name="rating_desc_bmi_severe_underweight">Is associated with very low body weight and increased risk of weakness, low energy, and impaired immune function. BMI does not account for muscle mass or fat distribution, though.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bmi_underweight">Is associated with low body weight and may increase the risk of fatigue, nutrient deficiencies, and reduced physical resilience. BMI does not account for muscle mass or fat distribution, though.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bmi_normal">Is associated with a healthy weight range and lower risk of weight-related health problems. BMI does not account for muscle mass or fat distribution, though.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bmi_overweight">Is associated with increased body weight and may increase health risks over time, especially for heart and metabolic health. BMI does not account for muscle mass or fat distribution, though.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bmi_obese_class_i">Is associated with higher body weight and increased risk of conditions such as heart disease and type 2 diabetes. BMI does not account for muscle mass or fat distribution, though.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bmi_obese_class_ii">Is associated with significantly increased body weight and a higher likelihood of serious health conditions. BMI does not account for muscle mass or fat distribution, though.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bmi_obese_class_iii">Is associated with very high body weight and a substantially increased risk of severe health complications. BMI does not account for muscle mass or fat distribution, though.</string>

    <!-- Rating Descriptions — Body Fat % (Male) -->
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_male_dangerously_low">Is associated with extremely low body fat and increased risk of hormonal imbalance and impaired body function. However, body fat percentage alone does not take fat distribution into account.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_male_essential_fat">Is associated with very low body fat and may reduce energy availability and physical resilience. However, body fat percentage alone does not take fat distribution into account.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_male_athletic">Is associated with low body fat and is commonly seen in physically trained individuals.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_male_fit">Is associated with a healthy level of body fat and good overall physical condition.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_male_acceptable">Is associated with a typical body fat range and mild to moderate health risk.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_male_high_body_fat">Is associated with high body fat and increased risk of metabolic and cardiovascular conditions. However, body fat percentage alone does not take fat distribution into account.</string>

    <!-- Rating Descriptions — Body Fat % (Female) -->
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_female_dangerously_low">Is associated with extremely low body fat and increased risk of hormonal disruption and menstrual irregularities. However, body fat percentage alone does not take fat distribution into account.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_female_essential_fat">Is associated with very low body fat and may impact hormone balance and energy levels. However, body fat percentage alone does not take fat distribution into account.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_female_athletic">Is associated with low body fat and is commonly seen in physically trained individuals.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_female_fit">Is associated with a healthy and sustainable body fat level.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_female_acceptable">Is associated with a typical body fat range and mild to moderate health risk.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_bodyfat_female_high_body_fat">Is associated with high body fat and increased risk of chronic health conditions. However, body fat percentage alone does not take fat distribution into account.</string>

    <!-- Rating Descriptions — Waist-Hip Ratio (Male) -->
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_male_low_risk">Is associated with lower abdominal fat and reduced risk of cardiovascular disease.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_male_moderate_risk">Is associated with moderate abdominal fat and mild increase in health risk.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_male_high_risk">Is associated with higher abdominal fat and increased risk of heart and metabolic conditions.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_male_very_high_risk">Is associated with high abdominal fat and a significantly increased risk of serious health conditions.</string>

    <!-- Rating Descriptions — Waist-Hip Ratio (Female) -->
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_female_low_risk">Is associated with lower abdominal fat and reduced health risk.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_female_moderate_risk">Is associated with moderate abdominal fat and mild increase in health risk.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_female_high_risk">Is associated with increased abdominal fat and higher risk of metabolic and cardiovascular conditions.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whr_female_very_high_risk">Is associated with high abdominal fat and a significantly increased risk of serious health issues.</string>

    <!-- Rating Descriptions — Waist-Height Ratio -->
    <string name="rating_desc_whtr_underweight_risk">Is associated with a low waist size relative to height and might indicate low body fat or underweight status. However, health risk cannot be determined from this measure alone.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whtr_healthy">Is associated with a healthy waist size and lower risk of metabolic disease.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whtr_increased_risk">Is associated with increased abdominal fat and mild to moderate health risk.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whtr_high_risk">Is associated with high abdominal fat and increased likelihood of health problems.</string>
    <string name="rating_desc_whtr_very_high_risk">Is associated with very high abdominal fat and a strong link to serious health risks.</string>
    <string name="cd_metric_info">Show measurement guidance</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_side_front">Front</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_side_back">Back</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_sex_abbreviation_male">M</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_sex_abbreviation_female">F</string>

    <string name="measurement_guidance_weight">Weigh yourself at <b>the same time of day (ideally in the morning after getting up and after using the toilet)</b> and without clothing or with very light clothing. Stand centered on the scale and remain still until the reading is stable.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_body_fat">Use a body fat scale and make sure you <b>stand barefoot with clean, dry feet on the electrodes</b>. Measure under the same conditions whenever possible (time of day, hydration), as the reading is strongly influenced by these factors.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_neck_circumference">Look straight ahead and relax your shoulders. Measure the neck circumference <b>directly below the larynx (Adam\'s apple)</b>. Keep the measuring tape horizontal.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: <b>directly below the Adam\'s apple</b>\n♀ Women: <b>at the narrowest point of the neck</b> (if the Adam\'s apple is not clearly visible)</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_chest_circumference">Stand upright and breathe normally - measure at the end of a normal exhale. The measuring tape should be horizontal.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: circumference <b>at nipple level</b>\n♀ Women: circumference <b>at the fullest part of the chest</b>; ideally wear an <b>unpadded bra or no bra</b></string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_waist_circumference">Find the lowest palpable rib of your rib cage and the highest point of your hip bone. Stand relaxed and breathe out normally. Measure the circumference <b>midway between the rib cage and hip</b>. Keep the measuring tape horizontal and do not pull it too tight.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_abdomen_circumference">Stand upright and relax your abdomen. Measure the circumference <b>directly at navel level</b>. The measuring tape should be horizontal.\n\n⚠️ Note: This measurement differs from the waist circumference - it is always taken at the navel.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_hip_circumference">Stand upright with feet together. Measure the circumference <b>at the widest point of the hips and buttocks</b>. Make sure the measuring tape remains horizontal.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_chest_skinfold">Grasp the skin <b>midway between the nipple and the fold that forms between the arm and chest</b> when the arm hangs down. Grasp so that the measured skin fold runs from the nipple toward the armpit.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>diagonally</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: <b>measure as described</b>\n♀ Women: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_abdomen_skinfold">Grasp the skin <b>approx. 2-3 cm to the right of the navel</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>vertically</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♂ Men: <b>measure as described</b>\n♀ Women: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_thigh_skinfold">Stand relaxed and shift your weight to the other leg. Grasp the skin <b>on the front of the thigh, approximately midway between the hip and the knee</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>vertically</b>.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_triceps_skinfold">Let the arm hang loosely. Grasp the skin <b>on the back of the upper arm, midway between the shoulder and elbow</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>vertically</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♀ Women: <b>measure as described</b>\n♂ Men: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
    <string name="measurement_guidance_suprailiac_skinfold">Grasp the skin <b>directly above the hip bone, running slightly diagonally downward toward the front</b>.\n\n⚠️ Important: The orientation of the fold matters! It is taken <b>diagonally</b>.\n\n<b>⚤ Difference by sex:</b>\n♀ Women: <b>measure as described</b>\n♂ Men: optional measurement - not required for the 3-point body fat analysis.</string>
</resources>
